<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cameron&#39;s CV</title>
    <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cameron&#39;s CV</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 11:29:25 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scraping product prices from the internet</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/ctscraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 11:29:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/ctscraper/</guid>
      <description>All summer long I have wanted to purchase a new grill. I did a ton of research, looking for the perfect combination of size, features, and longevity, and what I quickly found was that my last qualifier - longevity - was one of the most expensive qualities to buy for. Quality grills are expensive at current regular prices, perhaps I needed to wait for a sale. I just needed to find one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Tunes</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/babytunes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/babytunes/</guid>
      <description>As any new parent will tell you, there is no shortage of toys for babies that play music and/or make white noise to help them sleep. Between stuffed animals with built-in electronics, baby monitor cameras, and wind-up music boxes that we received as baby shower gifts, we had at least 5 music/noise generators around our baby&amp;rsquo;s room. Unfortunately, none of them worked very well.
Off the Shelf In the first few months, our baby - like most - stayed in our bedroom with us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Playlist Generator</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/dynamicplaylist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 12:29:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/dynamicplaylist/</guid>
      <description>The Problem I have been known to have something of an eclectic music taste. I can go from TOOL to Billy Eilish to Big K.R.I.T. to Nelly Furtado to Armin van Buuren without much consideration. While I occasionally end up going down a bit of a genre rabbit hole from time to time, generally I like the mix. I get bored if I listen to too much of the same genre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ontario COVID-19 Active Case Tracking</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/covid/</guid>
      <description>Like many people, I have been drawn to the vast amounts of data being made available by governments as they track the COVID-19 pandemic. As I progressed through the data loading and cleaning phases of learning data science, I thought there might be a cool opportunity for a quick visualization of the data I was playing with.
  While doing this I learned a ton about
 Locating and collecting data from the Ontario Government Cleaning and associating data where key fields were not used consistently Handling map data and simplifying geography so the leaflet didn&amp;rsquo;t end up being huge and take a long time to render How to handle geospatial data and render interactive maps with Leaflet How to create parameterized R Markdown reports  Read more about this on my github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 15:29:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and welcome! This is my first post to my CV site.
This site will serve as a landing page for projects I work on in my spare time You can expect to see some cool data analysis using R and python.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>