<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cameron&#39;s CV</title>
    <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cameron&#39;s CV</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 11:04:25 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UnsupervisedMethods</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/unsupervised/unsupervised_learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 11:04:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/unsupervised/unsupervised_learning/</guid>
      <description>Unsupervised Statistical Learning Methods Earlier this week I completed a Statistical Learning course from Stanford put on by Trevor Hastie and Rob Tibshirani. I was drawn to this course because I had stumbled upon An Introduction to Statistical Learning as I looked to learn more about how to measure, and perhaps more importantly, visualize the Quality data I was reviewing in my role as a Quality Manager. The following post is more or less the same as the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ontario COVID-19 Active Case Tracking</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/covid/</guid>
      <description>Like many people, I have been drawn to the vast amounts of data being made available by governments as they track the COVID-19 pandemic. As I progressed through the data loading and cleaning phases of learning data science, I thought there might be a cool opportunity for a quick visualization of the data I was playing with.
  While doing this I learned a ton about
 Locating and collecting data from the Ontario Government Cleaning and associating data where key fields were not used consistently Handling map data and simplifying geography so the leaflet didn&amp;rsquo;t end up being huge and take a long time to render How to use leaflet  Read more about this on my github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 15:29:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cameron.willmot.ca/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and welcome! This is my first post to my CV site.
This site will serve as a landing page for projects I work on in my spare time You can expect to see some cool data analysis using R and python.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>